<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>INOCEA Consulting Ltd.</title><link>https://inocea.consulting/</link><description>Recent content on INOCEA Consulting Ltd.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 06:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inocea.consulting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ough!</title><link>https://inocea.consulting/contact/error/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://inocea.consulting/contact/error/</guid><description>Sorry, we were not able to recieve your message. Please try it again.</description></item><item><title>Our Mission</title><link>https://inocea.consulting/mission/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://inocea.consulting/mission/</guid><description>Empowering Your Business for Success:
We help you overcome technical challenges and unleash your team&amp;rsquo;s potential. Our mission is to support small and medium-sized businesses in realizing their full potential through expert guidance in culture building, process optimization, and technical leadership. From remote-first strategies to technical due diligence, we provide the support you need to make informed decisions, increase developer productivity, and achieve your business goals.
Your company has a purpose.</description></item><item><title>Thank you!</title><link>https://inocea.consulting/contact/success/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://inocea.consulting/contact/success/</guid><description>Thank you for your email! We will get back to you as quickly as possible.
Have a nice day!
Get back to the main page here.</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://inocea.consulting/imprint/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:47:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://inocea.consulting/imprint/</guid><description>Information provided according to Sec. 5 German Telemedia Act (TMG): INOCEA Consulting Ltd.
Terra Santa 1, Office 7
6012 Larnaca
Cyprus
Registry: ΗΕ 432966
VAT ID: CY10432966V
Contact: Telephone: +357 95 951843
Email: info@inocea.consulting
Responsible for contents acc. to Sec. 55, para. 2 German Federal Broadcasting Agreement (RstV): INOCEA Consulting Ltd.
Terra Santa 1, Office 7
6012 Larnaca
Cyprus
Liability for Contents As service providers, we are liable for own contents of these websites according to Sec.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://inocea.consulting/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:47:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://inocea.consulting/privacy-policy/</guid><description>1. An overview of data protection General The following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our website. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below. Data collection on our website Who is responsible for the data collection on this website? The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator.</description></item></channel></rss>